A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Publications, SG 1, Series 13 FA285
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Reviews, 8
  - "Psychiatric Interviews with Children", December 28, 1946-May 12, 1948 (Box 65, Folder 761)
  - "Psychiatric Social Work", April 20, 1940-October 1946 (Box 65, Folder 762)
  - "Psychiatry for the Pediatrician", April 10, 1948-May 1951 (Box 65, Folder 763)
  - "Psychological Appraisal of Children with Cerebral Defects", 1960-February 27, 1961 (Box 65, Folder 764)
  - "Psychomotor Aspects of Mental Disease", October 1954-1956 (Box 65, Folder 765)
  - "Psychotherapy in General Medicine", August 10, 1946-February 12, 1949 (Box 65, Folder 766)
  - "Public Health Is People", March 20, 1950-April 1956 (Box 66, Folder 767)
  - "Public Health Nurse and Her Patient", May 20, 1940-May 1953 (Box 66, Folder 768)
  - "The Red Cell", May 9, 1963-October 14, 1963 (Box 66, Folder 769)
  - "Red Cell and Case Development Problems", August 1963 (Box 66, Folder 770)
  - "Rheumatic Fever", September 3, 1940-1949 (Box 66, Folder 771)
  - "Rheumatoid Arthritis", September 9, 1957-January 1959 (Box 66, Folder 772)
  - "Rochester Regional Hospital Council", April 1956-October 1957 (Box 66, Folder 773)
  - "Science of Personality", 1941-March 1950 (Box 66, Folder 774)
  - "Serological Fraction in Schizphrenia", December 1963 (Box 66, Folder 775)
  - "Small Community Hospitals", February 24, 1944-August 1952 (Box 66, Folder 776)
  - "Snow on Cholera", October 19, 1936-September 21, 1957 (Box 66, Folder 777)
  - "Social Medicine", February 21, 1949-June 1951 (Box 66, Folder 778)
  - "Solving School Health Problems", May 15, 1942-October 1950 (Box 66, Folder 779)
  - "Somatosensory Changes After Penetrating Brain Wounds in Man", March 1961-August 1963 (Box 66, Folder 780)
  - "The Student-Physician", October 12, 1957-January 1959 (Box 66, Folder 781)
  - "Studies in Schizophrenia", 1952-October 1956 (Box 66, Folder 782)
  - "Synovial Fluid Changes in Joint Disease", April 1953-April 1955 (Box 66, Folder 783)
  - "Teaching and Learning in Medical School", October 1961-June 1963 (Box 66, Folder 784)
  - "Teaching Comprehensive Medical Care", December 7, 1959-February 1962 (Box 66, Folder 785)
  - "Teaching Psychotherapeutic Medicine", December 12, 1947-January 1950 (Box 67, Folder 786)
  - "Thinking and Psychotherapy", March 4, 1961-November 24, 1961 (Box 67, Folder 787)
  - "Trends in Medical Education", June 10, 1949-July 1951 (Box 67, Folder 788)
  - "Tuberculosis in White and Negro Children", February 1, 1958-June 1960 (Box 67, Folder 789)
  - "Tutoring as Therapy", December 11, 1946-December 1949 (Box 67, Folder 790)
  - "Unraveling Juvenile Delinquency", October 1950-February 19, 1962 (Box 67, Folder 791)
  - "Unraveling Juvenile Delinquency", October 1950-February 19, 1962 (Box 67, Folder 792)
  - "Unraveling Juvenile Delinquency", October 1950-February 19, 1962 (Box 67, Folder 793)
  - "Unraveling Juvenile Delinquency", October 1950-February 19, 1962 (Box 67, Folder 794)
  - "Unraveling Juvenile Delinquency", October 1950-February 19, 1962 (Box 67, Folder 795)
  - "Visual Field Defects After Penetrating Missile Wounds of the Brain", 1960-March 1963 (Box 67, Folder 796)
  - "Vocational Rehabilitation of Psychiatric Patients", November 4, 1950-June 1953 (Box 67, Folder 797)
  - "Vocational Services for Psychiatric Clinic Patients", August 1952-July 1954 (Box 67, Folder 798)
  - "The War and Mental Health in England", June 27, 1944-June 1947 (Box 67, Folder 799)
  - "Ways to Community Health Education", December 30, 1939-May 1947 (Box 68, Folder 800)
  - "Widening Horizons in Medical Education", June 30, 1948-January 1951 (Box 68, Folder 801)
- Titles, 9
  This subseries is concerned with the practical publishing of various Commonwealth Fund books. The subseries consists of correspondence and financial papers which deal with such publishing matters as bindings, engraving and jackets. The folders date from the 1940s to the 1960s. Most of the books are reviewed in the Review subseries.
  - Acknowledgement Postcard, June 11-15, 1959 (Box 68, Folder 802)
  - "Advances in Rheumatic Fever" (May Wilson) - Correspondence, May 18, 1959-November 5, 1964 (Box 68, Folder 803)
  - "Advances in Rheumatic Fever" (May Wilson) - Distribution, February 19, 1962-January 28, 1964 (Box 68, Folder 804)
  - "Advances in Rheumatic Fever" (May Wilson) - Editorial, May 19, 1959-August 31, 1962 (Box 68, Folder 805)
  - "Advances in Rheumatic Fever" (May Wilson) - Permission to Quote, November 11, 1960-May 16, 1962 (Box 68, Folder 806)
  - "Advances in Rheumatic Fever" (May Wilson) - Production, March 4, 1960-June 25, 1963 (Box 68, Folder 807)
  - "Adventures in Medical Education" (George Canby Robinson) - Correspondence, August 15, 1956-February 5, 1959 (Box 68, Folder 808)
  - "Adventures in Medical Education" (George Canby Robinson) - Distribution, February 18, 1957-February 14, 1958 (Box 68, Folder 809)
  - "Adventures in Medical Education" (George Canby Robinson) - Editorial, March 27, 1957-August 20, 1958 (Box 68, Folder 810)
  - "Adventures in Medical Education" (George Canby Robinson) - Permission to Quote, June 5, 1957-September 12, 1957 (Box 68, Folder 811)
  - "Adventures in Medical Education" (George Canby Robinson) - Production, March 15, 1957-July 10, 1958 (Box 68, Folder 812)
  - "Airborne Contagion and Air Hygiene" (W. F. Wells) - Correspondence, March 26, 1941-June 29, 1950 (Box 68, Folder 813)
  - "Airborne Contagion and Air Hygiene" (W. F. Wells) - Correspondence, July 10, 1950-October 23, 1964 (Box 69, Folder 814)
  - "Airborne Contagion and Air Hygiene" (W. F. Wells) - Correspondence, July 10, 1950-October 23, 1964 (Box 69, Folder 815)
  - "Airborne Contagion and Air Hygiene" (W. F. Wells) - Correspondence, July 10, 1950-October 23, 1964 (Box 69, Folder 816)
  - "Airborne Contagion and Air Hygiene" (W. F. Wells) - Correspondence, July 10, 1950-October 23, 1964 (Box 69, Folder 817)
  - "Airborne Contagion and Air Hygiene" (W. F. Wells) - Correspondence, July 10, 1950-October 23, 1964 (Box 69, Folder 818)
  - "Airborne Contagion and Air Hygiene" (W. F. Wells) - Permission to Quote, June 14, 1940-January 29, 1955 (Box 69, Folder 819)
  - "Airborne Contagion and Air Hygiene" (W. F. Wells) - Printing and Production, July 17, 1953-February 3, 1956 (Box 69, Folder 820)
  - "Airborne Contagion and Air Hygiene" (W. F. Wells) - Sales Promotion, July 13, 1954-June 4, 1955 (Box 69, Folder 821)
  - "Airborne Infection" - Correspondence, October 31, 1936-November 21, 1961 (Box 70, Folder 822)
  - "Airborne Infection" - First and Second Printing, December 11, 1942-May 5, 1947 (Box 70, Folder 823)
  - "American Medical Practice" - Circulation and Distribution, September 28, 1944-April 21, 1945 (Box 70, Folder 824)
  - "American Medical Practice" - Correspondence, June 28, 1944-December 11, 1961 (Box 70, Folder 825)
  - "American Medical Practice" - First, Second and Third Printing, June 30, 1944-June 28, 1946 (Box 70, Folder 826)
  - "American Medical Research" - Circulation and Distribution, July 2, 1947-February 6, 1948 (Box 70, Folder 827)
  - "American Medical Research" - Correspondence, March 10, 1947-December 13, 1967 (Box 70, Folder 828)
  - "American Medical Research" - Printing, June 25, 1947-December 4, 1947 (Box 70, Folder 829)
  - Annual Report (Correspondence and Production), 1921-1946 (Box 70, Folder 830)
  - Annual Report (Correspondence and Production), 1921-1946 (Box 70, Folder 831)
  - Annual Report (Correspondence and Production), 1921-1946 (Box 70, Folder 832)
  - Annual Report (Correspondence and Production), 1921-1946 (Box 70, Folder 833)
  - Annual Report (Correspondence and Production), 1921-1946 (Box 70, Folder 834)
  - Annual Report (Correspondence and Production), 1921-1946 (Box 70, Folder 835)
  - Annual Report (Correspondence and Production), 1921-1946 (Box 70, Folder 836)
  - Annual Report (Correspondence and Production), 1921-1946 (Box 70, Folder 837)
  - Annual Report (Correspondence and Production), 1921-1946 (Box 70, Folder 838)
  - Annual Report (Correspondence and Production), 1921-1946 (Box 70, Folder 839)
  - Annual Report (Correspondence and Production), 1947-1975 (Box 71, Folder 840)
  - Annual Report (Correspondence and Production), 1947-1975 (Box 71, Folder 841)
  - Annual Report (Correspondence and Production), 1947-1975 (Box 71, Folder 842)
  - Annual Report (Correspondence and Production), 1947-1975 (Box 71, Folder 843)
  - Annual Report (Correspondence and Production), 1947-1975 (Box 71, Folder 844)
  - Annual Report (Correspondence and Production), 1947-1975 (Box 71, Folder 845)
  - Annual Report (Correspondence and Production), 1947-1975 (Box 71, Folder 846)
  - Annual Report (Correspondence and Production), 1947-1975 (Box 71, Folder 847)
  - Annual Report (Correspondence and Production), 1947-1975 (Box 71, Folder 848)
  - Annual Report (Correspondence and Production), 1947-1975 (Box 71, Folder 849)
  - Annual Report (Correspondence and Production), 1947-1975 (Box 71, Folder 850)
  - Annual Report (Correspondence and Production), 1947-1975 (Box 71, Folder 851)
  - Annual Report (Correspondence and Production), 1947-1975 (Box 71, Folder 852)
  - Annual Report (Correspondence and Production), 1947-1975 (Box 71, Folder 853)
  - Annual Report (Correspondence and Production), 1947-1975 (Box 71, Folder 854)
  - Annual Report (Correspondence and Production), 1947-1975 (Box 71, Folder 855)
  - Annual Report (Correspondence and Production), 1947-1975 (Box 71, Folder 856)
  - Annual Report (Costs - Binding), 1930-1976 (Box 72, Folder 857)
  - Annual Report (Costs - Binding), 1930-1976 (Box 72, Folder 858)
  - Annual Report (Mailing List and Distribution), June 29, 1956-October 2, 1959 (Box 72, Folder 859)
  - Annual Report (Paper), September 1, 1933-August 2, 1966 (Box 72, Folder 860)
  - "Aphasia" (Katharine E. McBride and Theodore H. Weisenburg), December 17, 1930-June 5, 1963 (Box 72, Folder 861)
  - "Aphasia" (Katharine E. McBride and Theodore H. Weisenburg) - Printing, January 25, 1935-April 19, 1944 (Box 72, Folder 862)
  - "Atlas of Exfoliative Cytology" - Correspondence, September 25, 1946-June 11, 1969 (Box 72, Folder 863)
  - "Atlas of Exfoliative Cytology" - Correspondence, September 25, 1946-June 11, 1969 (Box 72, Folder 864)
  - "Atlas of Exfoliative Cytology" - Illustrations, June 13, 1949-May 23, 1960 (Box 72, Folder 865)
  - "Atlas of Exfoliative Cytology" - Printing (Connecticut Printers), December 5, 1950-August 24, 1954 (Box 72, Folder 866)
  - "Atlas of Exfoliative Cytology" - Printing (Harvard University Press), December 13, 1951-April 1, 1977 (Box 72, Folder 867)
  - "Atlas of Exfoliative Cytology" - Sales Promotion, January 21, 1952-April 29, 1954 (Box 73, Folder 868)
  - "Atlas of Exfoliative Cytology" - Supplement I (Plates), March 4, 1954-October 10, 1963 (Box 73, Folder 869)
  - "Atlas of Exfoliative Cytology" - Supplement I (Plates), March 4, 1954-October 10, 1963 (Box 73, Folder 870)
  - "Atlas of Exfoliative Cytology" - Supplement I (Plates), March 4, 1954-October 10, 1963 (Box 73, Folder 871)
  - "Atlas of Exfoliative Cytology" - Supplement II (Production and Correspondence), September 13, 1956-April 10, 1963 (Box 73, Folder 872)
  - "Atlas of Exfoliative Cytology" - Supplement II (Production and Correspondence), September 13, 1956-April 10, 1963 (Box 73, Folder 873)
  - "Atlas of Exfoliative Cytology" - Supplement II (Production and Correspondence), September 13, 1956-April 10, 1963 (Box 73, Folder 874)
  - "Atlas of the Blood in Children" - Circulation and Distribution, January 20, 1942-February 11, 1960 (Box 73, Folder 875)
  - "Atlas of the Blood in Children" - Correspondence, December 23, 1935-April 6, 1969 (Box 73, Folder 876)
  - "Atlas of the Blood in Children" - Correspondence, December 23, 1935-April 6, 1969 (Box 73, Folder 877)
  - "Atlas of the Blood in Children" - Correspondence, December 23, 1935-April 6, 1969 (Box 73, Folder 878)
  - "Atlas of the Blood in Children" - First Printing, November 22, 1938-December 14, 1942 (Box 73, Folder 879)
  - "Atlas of the Blood in Children" - First Printing, January 14, 1943-January 29, 1945 (Box 74, Folder 880)
  - "Atlas of the Blood in Children" - First Printing, January 14, 1943-January 29, 1945 (Box 74, Folder 881)
  - "Atlas of the Blood in Children" - Second Printing, January 30, 1945-July 25, 1946 (Box 74, Folder 882)
  - "Atlas of the Blood in Children" - Third Printing, November 26, 1946-May 4, 1953 (Box 74, Folder 883)
  - "Biology of Pneumococcus" - First and Second Printing, December 17, 1930-October 15, 1965 (Box 74, Folder 884)
  - "Biology of Pneumococcus" - First and Second Printing, December 17, 1930-October 15, 1965 (Box 74, Folder 885)
  - Board Report, September 12, 1947-May 26, 1954 (Box 74, Folder 886)
  - Board Report (Miscellaneous), April 10, 1933-December 9, 1949 (Box 74, Folder 887)
  - Bookplate, February 26, 1954-November 6, 1958 (Box 74, Folder 888)
  - Bowker, R. H. Company, February 3, 1950-May 9, 1952 (Box 74, Folder 889)
  - "Brucella Infections in Animals and Man" - Correspondence, August 12, 1930-July 11, 1951 (Box 74, Folder 890)
  - "Brucella Infections in Animals and Man" - Printing, June 9, 1933-August 8, 1934 (Box 74, Folder 891)
  - "Brucellosis in Man and Animals" - Correspondence, December 12, 1938-January 30, 1940 (Box 74, Folder 892)
  - "Brucellosis in Man and Animals" - Correspondence (1943 Revised Edition), August 10, 1941-May 8, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 893)
  - "Brucellosis in Man and Animals" - Printing, December 22, 1938-June 3, 1940 (Box 74, Folder 894)
  - "Brucellosis in Man and Animals" - Second and Third Printing, August 4, 1942-February 28, 1952 (Box 75, Folder 895)
  - "Building Regulations in New York City" - Correspondence, April 6, 1936-November 19, 1971 (Box 75, Folder 896)
  - "Building Regulations in New York City" - Printing, December 31, 1941-March 6, 1944 (Box 75, Folder 897)
  - "Cancer in Families" - Correspondence, December 18, 1951-July 11, 1960 (Box 75, Folder 898)
  - "Cancer in Families" - Correspondence, December 18, 1951-July 11, 1960 (Box 75, Folder 899)
  - "Cancer in Families" - Correspondence, December 18, 1951-July 11, 1960 (Box 75, Folder 900)
  - "Cancer in Families" - Distribution, January 23, 1959-December 8, 1959 (Box 75, Folder 901)
  - "Cancer in Families" - Editorial, July 28, 1955-March 24, 1959 (Box 75, Folder 902)
  - "Cancer in Families" - Permission to Quote, March 19-25, 1959 (Box 75, Folder 903)
  - "Cancer in Families" - Production, October 24, 1955-September 11, 1959 (Box 75, Folder 904)
  - "Cardiac Catheterization in Congenital Heart Disease" - Circulation and Distribution, November 16, 1948-February 8, 1951 (Box 75, Folder 905)
  - "Cardiac Catheterization in Congenital Heart Disease" - Correspondence, July 15, 1948-December 12, 1959 (Box 75, Folder 906)
  - "Cardiac Catheterization in Congenital Heart Disease" - First Printing, February 9, 1948-August 31, 1950 (Box 75, Folder 907)
  - "Cardiac Catheterization in Congenital Heart Disease" - Second Printing, March 20, 1950-April 30, 1954 (Box 76, Folder 908)
  - "Care of the Long Term Patient" (Commission on Chronic Illness) Chronic Illness in U.S., Volume II - Correspondence, April 15, 1954-April 18, 1958 (Box 76, Folder 909)
  - "Care of the Long Term Patient" (Commission on Chronic Illness) Chronic Illness in U.S., Volume II - Correspondence, April 15, 1954-April 18, 1958 (Box 76, Folder 910)
  - "Care of the Long Term Patient" (Commission on Chronic Illness) Chronic Illness in U.S., Volume II - Printing, August 29, 1955-February 27, 1958 (Box 76, Folder 911)
  - "Care of the Long Term Patient" (Commission on Chronic Illness) Chronic Illness in U.S., Volume II - Sales Promotion, March 21, 1956-April 30, 1958 (Box 76, Folder 912)
  - "Case Development Problems in Hematology" (John W. Harris and Daniel L. Horrigan) - Correspondence, June 14, 1962-April 28, 1965 (Box 76, Folder 913)
  - "Case Development Problems in Hematology" (John W. Harris and Daniel L. Horrigan) - Distribution, October 4, 1962-November 5, 1964 (Box 76, Folder 914)
  - "Case Development Problems in Hematology" (John W. Harris and Daniel L. Horrigan) - Editorial, June 25, 1962-October 29, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 915)
  - "Case Development Problems in Hematology" (John W. Harris and Daniel L. Horrigan) - Permission to Quote, October 12, 1942 (Box 76, Folder 916)
  - "Case Development Problems in Hematology" (John W. Harris and Daniel L. Horrigan) - Production, August 10, 1962-January 29, 1963 (Box 76, Folder 917)
  - "Chemotherapy and Serum Therapy of Pneumonia" - Correspondence and Printing, October 9, 1939-September 31, 1941 (Box 76, Folder 918)
  - "Child Health Services and Pediatric Education" - Circulation and Distribution (C), September 15, 1948-April 28, 1949 (Box 76, Folder 919)
  - "Child Health Services and Pediatric Education" - Circulation and Distribution (D), September 24, 1948-February 16, 1951 (Box 77, Folder 920)
  - "Child Health Services and Pediatric Education" - Correspondence, May 28, 1947-October 5, 1951 (Box 77, Folder 921)
  - "Child Health Services and Pediatric Education" - Miscellaneous Pamphlets, September 7, 1948 (Box 77, Folder 922)
  - "Child Health Services and Pediatric Education" - Printing, August 3, 1948-June 13, 1951 (Box 77, Folder 923)
  - "Child Health Services and Pediatric Education" - Supplementary Material, December 2, 1948-September 10, 1961 (Box 77, Folder 924)
  - "Child Health Services and Pediatric Education" - Supplementary Material, December 2, 1948-September 10, 1961 (Box 77, Folder 925)
  - "Child Health Services and Pediatric Education" - Supplementary Material, December 2, 1948-September 10, 1961 (Box 77, Folder 926)
  - "Child Research Council" (Alfred H. Washburn), May 17, 1935-May 26, 1938 (Box 77, Folder 927)
  - "Childhood Schizophrenia" (William Goldfarb) - Correspondence, June 30, 1960-February 14, 1968 (Box 77, Folder 928)
  - "Childhood Schizophrenia" (William Goldfarb) - Distribution, March 6, 1961-February 9, 1962 (Box 77, Folder 929)
  - "Childhood Schizophrenia" (William Goldfarb) - Editorial, October 4, 1960-December 22, 1961 (Box 77, Folder 930)
  - "Childhood Schizophrenia" (William Goldfarb) - Production, November 16, 1960-February 27, 1962 (Box 77, Folder 931)
  - "Children's Behavior and Teachers' Attitudes", July 28, 1928-August 19, 1955 (Box 77, Folder 932)
  - "Chronic Illness in a Large City: The Baltimore Study" (Commission on Chronic Illness) Chronic Illness in the U.S., Volume IV, August 22, 1956-February 10, 1958 (Box 78, Folder 933)
  - "Chronic Illness in a Large City: The Baltimore Study" (Commission on Chronic Illness) Chronic Illness in the U.S., Volume IV, August 22, 1956-February 10, 1958 (Box 78, Folder 934)
  - "Chronic Illness in a Large City: The Batimore Study" (Commission on Chronic Illness) Chronic Illness in the U.S., Volume IV, August 22, 1956-February 10, 1958 (Box 78, Folder 935)
  - "Chronic Illness in a Large City: The Baltimore Study" (Commission on Chronic Illness) Chronic Illness in the U.S., Volume IV, August 22, 1956-February 10, 1958 (Box 78, Folder 936)
  - "Chronic Illness in a Rural Area: The Hunterdon Study" (Commission on Chronic Illness) Chronic Illness in the U.S., Volume III, January 21, 1957-October 23, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 937)
  - "Chronic Illness in a Rural Area: The Hunterdon Study" (Commission on Chronic Illness) Chronic Illness in the U.S., Volume III, January 21, 1957-October 23, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 938)
  - "Chronic Illness in a Rural Area: The Hunterdon Study" (Commission on Chronic Illness) Chronic Illness in the U.S., Volume III, January 21, 1957-October 23, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 939)
  - "Chronic Illness in a Rural Area: The Hunterdon Study" (Commission on Chronic Illness) Chronic Illness in the U.S., Volume III, January 21, 1957-October 23, 1961 (Box 78, Folder 940)
  - "Closed Ranks" - Correspondence, May 7, 1953-July 20, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 941)
  - "Closed Ranks" - Correspondence, May 7, 1953-July 20, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 942)
  - "Closed Ranks" - Correspondence, May 7, 1953-July 20, 1956 (Box 78, Folder 943)
  - "Closed Ranks" - Correspondence, August 22, 1956-January 29, 1968 (Box 79, Folder 944)
  - "Closed Ranks" - Distribution, March 14, 1956-April 1, 1958 (Box 79, Folder 945)
  - "Closed Ranks" - Editorial, October 19, 1956-April 11, 1957 (Box 79, Folder 946)
  - "Closed Ranks" - Production, September 6, 1956-April 11, 1957 (Box 79, Folder 947)
  - Commonwealth Fund Announcement Card, June 18, 1963-September 1, 1963 (Box 79, Folder 948)
  - Commonwealth Fund Booklet, December 11, 1945-August 31, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 949)
  - Commonwealth Fund Booklet, December 11, 1945-August 31, 1964 (Box 79, Folder 950)
  - Commonwealth Fund Complimentary Cards, March 21, 1946-May 27, 1975 (Box 79, Folder 951)
  - Commonwealth Fund Device, February 1, 1952-June 16, 1959 (Box 79, Folder 952)
  - Commonwealth Fund from the Desk of Quigg Newton, November 8, 1953 (Box 79, Folder 953)
  - "Community Health Organization" (1932 and 1939 Editions) - Correspondence, November 17, 1931-April 29, 1939 (Box 79, Folder 954)
  - "Community Health Organization" (Revision) - Correspondence (C-P), November 14, 1941-October 25, 1962 (Box 79, Folder 955)
  - "Community Health Organization" (Revision) - Correspondence (R), May 5, 1949-November 15, 1954 (Box 80, Folder 956)
  - "Community Programs for Mental Health" - Correspondence, October 1, 1950-November 14, 1955 (Box 80, Folder 957)
  - "Community Programs for Mental Health" - Permission to Quote, December 23, 1954-July 1, 1955 (Box 80, Folder 958)
  - "Community Programs for Mental Health" - Printing and Production, November 16, 1954-November 19, 1956 (Box 80, Folder 959)
  - "Community Programs for Mental Health" - Sales Promotion, March 15, 1955-January 31, 1956 (Box 80, Folder 960)
  - "Congenital Malformation of the Heart" - Circulation and Distribution, October 20, 1947-February 13, 1951 (Box 80, Folder 961)
  - "Congenital Malformation of the Heart" - Correspondence, April 29, 1938-May 24, 1944 (Box 80, Folder 962)
  - "Congenital Malformation of the Heart" - Correspondence, April 29, 1938-May 24, 1944 (Box 80, Folder 963)
  - "Congenital Malformation of the Heart" - Correspondence, April 29, 1938-May 24, 1944 (Box 80, Folder 964)
  - "Congenital Malformation of the Heart" - Correspondence, June 1, 1944-February 24, 1948 (Box 81, Folder 965)
  - "Congenital Malformation of the Heart" - Correspondence, June 1, 1944-February 24, 1948 (Box 81, Folder 966)
  - "Congenital Malformation of the Heart" - Correspondence, June 1, 1944-February 24, 1948 (Box 81, Folder 967)
  - "Congenital Malformation of the Heart" - Illustrations, June 27, 1941-May 4, 1953 (Box 81, Folder 968)
  - "Congenital Malformation of the Heart" - Printing, May 9, 1941-August 18, 1954 (Box 81, Folder 969)
  - "Congenital Malformation of the Heart" - Printing, May 9, 1941-August 18, 1954 (Box 81, Folder 970)
  - "Congenital Malformation of the Heart" - Printing, May 9, 1941-August 18, 1954 (Box 81, Folder 971)
  - "Congenital Malformation of the Heart" - Revised Edition Volume I (Correspondence), February 17, 1948-December 2, 1958 (Box 81, Folder 972)
  - "Congenital Malformation of the Heart" - Revised Edition Volume I (Correspondence), April 15, 1959-April 13, 1966 (Box 82, Folder 973)
  - "Congenital Malformation of the Heart" - Revised Edition Volume I (Distribution), June 25, 1959-December 15, 1960 (Box 82, Folder 974)
  - "Congenital Malformation of the Heart" - Revised Edition Volume I (Editorial), November 18, 1958-March 7, 1961 (Box 82, Folder 975)
  - "Congenital Malformation of the Heart" - Revised Edition Volume I (Production), June 2, 1952-April 4, 1961 (Box 82, Folder 976)